COVID-19 Pandemic Collection MS269
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- COVID-19 pandemic collection, circa 1949 -- 1953, 2003, 2020; 2020; MS269.000001; 11.7 Gigabytes; 166 Digital Object(s) Of the 166 digital objects, one digital object comprises 98 files.; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts campus photographs and COVID-19 reflection, 2020 March -- June; MS269.000009; 143.1 Megabytes; 27 Digital Object(s)
    - Tisch Library closing sign, 2020 March 11; MS269.000029; 2.4 Megabytes
      The University initially announced that Tisch Library would be restricted to students and staff beginning on March 16. The announcement was revised a day later to institute a complete closure of the library.
    - Tufts Daily Spring 2020 deadlines, 2020 March 11; MS269.000030; 2.4 Megabytes
      The Daily's deadline records for the spring 2020 semester.
    - Students waiting in line for boxes, 2020 March 12; MS269.000031; 4.3 Megabytes
      Students line up for boxes after being told they had a few days to move out of their dormitories.
    - Empty Commons Marketplace, 2020 March 19; MS269.000032; 3 Megabytes
      The Commons Marketplace is pictured. Along with Dewick, the Commons was the only dining location to remain open after the university closed. Chairs were removed after Massachusetts banned dining inside restaurants.
    - Bromfield Road graduation, 2020 May 17; MS269.000033; 9.5 Megabytes
      Bromfield Road graduation. The student in front holding the speaker was playing "Pomp and Circumstance."
    - Bromfield Road graduation, 2020 May 17; MS269.000034; 8.5 Megabytes
      Bromfield Road graduation.
    - Bromfield Road graduation, 2020 May 17; MS269.000035; 8.4 Megabytes
    - COVID-19 reflections, 2020 June; MS269.000036; 62.6 Megabytes
  - COVID-19 pandemic obituaries, 2020 May 11; MS269.000037; 356 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s); 8 Minutes
    Transferred by Silvia Bottinelli, June 2020, accession number MS-2020-069.
    TRT World interview with School of Museum of Fine Arts professor, Silvia Bottinnelli, on the critic and curator Germano Celant, who died of coronavirus.
  - As Life Goes On student film, 2020 June; MS269.000171; 2.37 Gigabytes; 5 Minutes
    Transferred by Annie Ziwen Yin, June 2020, accession number MS-2021-001.
    Film project created by Annie Ziwen Yin for Film and Media Studies 34: Producing for Film. Participants filmed snippets of their lives during the COVID-19 pandemic and Yin compiled and edited the footage. Participants, who were both Tufts and non-Tufts students, were located in Chicago, Illinois; Longmeadow, New York; New York City, New York; Philadelphia, Pennsylvania; Seattle, Washington; Brisbane, Australia; Beijing, China; Copenhagen, Denmark; Astana, Kazakhstan; and Singapore.
  - Beth and Vincent Maniero letters and photographs, circa 1949 -- 1953, 2003, 2020; 2020; MS269.000124; 11.6 Megabytes; 50 Digital Object(s)
    Transferred by Elizabeth Mainiero, July 2020, accession number MS-2021-002.
    Letters written by Beth Mainiero to her husband, Vincent Mainiero, Tufts Class of 1953. Vincent was in a nursing home and because he was unable to use the phone due to his health or receive visits due to the pandemic, Beth wrote him letters. The letters recount Beth's day-to-day activities during the pandemic; greetings from friends and family; summaries of communications from the nursing home; and information about Vincent's health. Vincent died of COVID-19 on May 12, 2020. This material also includes scanned photographs of Vincent, a scanned map of the Tufts campus, and statistics regarding nursing home deaths due to COVID-19 in Milford, Connecticut.
    - Letter 0 to Vincent, pre-lockdown, 2020 February 08; MS269.000125; 13.8 Megabytes
    - Letter 1 to Vincent during shutdown, 2020 March 12; MS269.000126; 1.1 Megabytes
    - Letter 2 of virus shutdown, 2020 March 14; MS269.000127; 13.4 Kilobytes
    - Letter 3 to Vincent during virus lockdown, 2020 March 16; MS269.000128; 15 Kilobytes
    - Letter 4 to Vincent during lockdown, 2020 March 18; MS269.000129; 13.6 Kilobytes
    - Letter 5 to Vincent during virus lockdown, 2020 March 19; MS269.000130; 15.3 Kilobytes
    - Letter 6 to Vincent during shutdown, 2020 March 20; MS269.000131; 13.8 Kilobytes
    - Letter 7 to Vincent during Corona viruse, 2020 March 21; MS269.000132; 13.8 Kilobytes
    - Letter 8 to Vincent during virus, 2020 March 23; MS269.000133; 13.8 Kilobytes
    - Letter 9 to Vincent during virus crisis, 2020 March 24; MS269.000134; 39.5 Kilobytes
    - Letter 10 to Vincent during viruscrissis, 2020 March 25; MS269.000135; 13.5 Kilobytes
    - Letter 11 to Vincent during Corvid 19 virus, 2020 March 26; MS269.000136; 15.4 Kilobytes
    - Letter 11 to Vincent during virus, no more hand delivery use US Mail, 2020 March 27; MS269.000137; 592.1 Kilobytes
    - Letter 12 to Vincent during virus, 2020 March 28; MS269.000138; 14.1 Kilobytes
    - Letter 13 to Vincent during virus crisis, 2020 March 29; MS269.000139; 951.2 Kilobytes
    - Letter 14 to Vincent during virus, 2020 March 29; MS269.000140; 17.2 Kilobytes
    - Letter 15 to Vincent during shutdown, 2020 March 31; MS269.000141; 1.2 Megabytes
    - Letter 16 to Vincent during virus crisis, 2020 April 01; MS269.000142; 13.4 Kilobytes
    - Letter 17 to Vincent during virus outbreak, 2020 April 02; MS269.000143; 14.3 Kilobytes
    - Letter 18 to Vincent during COVID-19 virus, 2020 April 03; MS269.000144; 773.2 Kilobytes
    - Letter 19 to Vincent during COVID-19 flu, 2020 April 05; MS269.000145; 14.4 Kilobytes
    - Letter 20 to Vincent during shutdown, 2020 April 06; MS269.000146; 1.0 Megabytes
    - Letter 21 during COVID-19 virus to Vincent, 2020 April 07; MS269.000147; 12.0 Kilobytes
    - Letter 22 to Vincent during shutdown, 2020 April 08; MS269.000148; 1.3 Megabytes
    - Letter 23 to Vincent during COVID-19 virus, 2020 April 09; MS269.000149; 13.9 Kilobytes
    - Letter 24 to Vincent during COVID-19 outbreak, 2020 April 10; MS269.000150; 13.8 Kilobytes
    - Letter 25 to Vincent during virus crisis about why he cannot come home, copy 2, 2020 April 11; MS269.000151; 25.6 Kilobytes
    - Letter 26 to Vincent during COVID-19 virus, 2020 April 15; MS269.000152; 13.9 Kilobytes
    - Letter 27 to Vincent during COVID-19 virus, 2020 April 16; MS269.000153; 13.9 Kilobytes
    - Letter 28 during COVID virus to Vincent, 2020 April 18; MS269.000154; 17.5 Kilobytes
    - Letter 29a during COVID-19 virus outbreak to Vincent, 2020 April 19; MS269.000155; 13.5 Kilobytes
    - Letter 29b to Vincent during COVID-19 virus outbreak, 2020 April 20; MS269.000156; 23.1 Kilobytes
    - Letter 30 to Vincent during flu epidemic, 2020 April 21; MS269.000157; 14.2 Kilobytes
    - Letter 31 to Vincent during COVID-19 virus shutdown, 2020 April 22; MS269.000158; 31.3 Kilobytes
    - Letter 33 to Vincent during COVID-19, 2020 April 25; MS269.000159; 13.1 Kilobytes
    - Letter 34 to Vincent, 2020 April 26; MS269.000160; 13.3 Kilobytes
    - Letter 35 to Vincent during COVID-19 virus, 2020 April 27; MS269.000161; 14.3 Kilobytes
    - Letter 36 to Vincent, 2020 April 28; MS269.000162; 14.5 Kilobytes
    - Letter 37 during virus, 2020 April 30; MS269.000163; 356.4 Kilobytes
    - Letter 38 to Vincent during COVID-19, 2020 May 01; MS269.000164; 13.4 Kilobytes
    - Letter 39 to Vincent during COVID-19, 2020 May 02; MS269.000165; 13.5 Kilobytes
    - Letter 40 to Vincent during COVID-19 shutdown, 2020 May 04; MS269.000166; 14.8 Kilobytes
    - Letter 41 to Vincent during COVID-19 shutdown, 2020 May 05; MS269.000167; 13.6 Kilobytes
    - Letter 42 to Vincent during COVID-19 shutdown, 2020 May 06; MS269.000168; 14.4 Kilobytes
    - Letter 43 to Vincent during COVID-19 shutdown, 2020 May 08; MS269.000169; 13.5 Kilobytes
    - Letter 44 to Vincent during COVID-19 shutdown, 2020 May 09; MS269.000170; 16.0 Kilobytes
    - Milford, Connecticut COVID-19 nursing home deaths statistics, 2020 June 14; MS269.000178; 14 Kilobytes
    - Tufts campus map, circa 1949 -- 1953; MS269.000179; 2.8 Megabytes
    - Vincent Mainiero photographs, circa 1949 -- 1953; MS269.000180; 915.7 Kilobytes
    - Vincent Mainiero and friend Bill at Tufts Class of 1953 reunion, 2003; MS269.000181; 188 Kilobytes
  - Tufts Community Union Senate survey, report, and raw data, 2020 June -- 2020 July; MS269.000119; Tufts Community Union Senate; 8.6 Megabytes; 3 Digital Object(s)
    Transferred by Sarah Weiner, July 2020, accession number MS-2021-003.
    Tufts Community Union Senate survey, report, and raw data, consisting of survey questions and responses, a publicly distributed final narrative report, and the raw data. The survey asked students what they thought did and did not go well during the start of the pandemic in Spring 2020, fears and concerns about the upcoming Fall 2020 semester, and what aspects of student life were most important to try to maintain in the Fall 2020 semester.
    - Fall 2020 student feedback survey report, 2020 June 21; MS269.000120; Tufts Community Union Senate; 145 Kilobytes
    - Fall 2020 student feedback survey default report, 2020 June 21; MS269.000121; Tufts Community Union Senate; 4.6 Megabytes
    - Fall 2020 survey raw data, 2020 July 07; MS269.000122; Tufts Community Union Senate; 3.8 Megabytes
  - Tony Monaco correspondence and photographs, 2020 June; MS269.000172; 20.4 Megabytes; 1 Digital Object(s)
    20 years from date of creation.
    Transferred by Tony Monaco, June 2020, accession number UA-2021-005.
  - Tufts University Social Collective socially distanced graduation and Senior Week material, 2020; MS269.000173; 3.3 Gigabytes; 3 Digital Object(s) Of the three digital objects in this file, one digital object comprises 98 files.
    Transferred by John Wescott, June 2020, accession number UA-2021-002.
    Photos and videos depicting a socially distanced graduation ceremony for the graduating members of the Tufts University Social Collective (TUSC) and Senior Week material created by TUSC. The Senior Week material consists of items mailed to each graduating student in a "Senior Week in a Box" and a list of the contents.
    - Socially distanced graduation ceremony photographs and videos, 2020 May; MS269.000174; 3.3 Gigabytes; 1 Digital Object(s) One digital object comprising 98 files.
    - Senior Week in a Box, 2020; MS269.000175; 1 Linear Feet
    - Senior Week in a Box insert, 2020; MS269.000176; 84.1 Kilobytes
    - Senior Week 2020 flyer, 2020 May; MS269.000177; 275 Kilobytes
  - Commencement website capture, 2020 May; MS269.000038; 1 Web sites WARC file contains captured of each school's 2020 commencement ceremony, excluding the well-wishing videos submitted by friends, family, faculty, and staff.; 2 Gigabytes
    This web capture represents the commencement ceremonies for each school at Tufts as they were held online in 2020 due to the COVID-19 pandemic. The capture does not include the well-wisher videos submitted by family, friends, faculty, and staff to each school.
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Webrecorder Player is needed to playback the website content. Instuctions for download and use are in the Box folder linked from this record.
- Web crawls, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-10-06; MS269.000182; 365 Web sites
  This series is arranged chronologically by the date a website was first crawled.
  This series is open for research.
  This series represents a collection of websites regarding Tufts University's response to the COVID-19 pandemic in 2020. Websites include official University communications, news items reporting on Tufts' response, student-published articles, and social media posts.
  The collection will grow as the pandemic continues, and the finding aid will be updated on a regular basis to reflect addtions. To see the current state of the web collection, follow the link in the Other Finding Aids note for this series to its Archive-It landing page.
  Other Finding Aids
  To see all of websites crawled as part of the Tufts response to COVID-19 web collection, please visit https://archive-it.org/collections/13686
  - Admitted Students: COVID-19 Guidance, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-03-31; MS269.000183; Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, School of Engineering; 1 Web sites
    General
    Frequency: One-time crawl
  - Community Partnerships - Coronavirus (COVID-19), 2020-03-18 -- 2020-10-06; MS269.000184; Tufts University; 1 Web sites
    Frequency: Weekly crawl
  - Coronavirus (COVID-19), 2020-03-18 -- 2020-10-06; MS269.000185; Tufts University; 1 Web sites
    Frequency: Daily crawl
  - Coronavirus Planning Update, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-03-31; MS269.000186; Office of the President; 1 Web sites
  - Coronavirus Tufts: Frequently Asked Questions, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-10-06; MS269.000187; Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - Coronavirus Updates, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-09-15; MS269.000188; School of Dental Medicine; 1 Web sites
    Frequency: Monthly crawl
  - COVID-19 Communications and Guidance, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-10-06; MS269.000189; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 Guidance, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-08-31; MS269.000190; Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, School of Engineering; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 GUIDANCE: Latest Updates Cummings School and Tufts University, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-06-23; MS269.000191; Cummings Veterinary Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 Update, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-05-20; MS269.000192; Undergraduate Admissions; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 update: Significant and immediate changes to Tufts' operations, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-03-31; MS269.000193; Office of the President; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19: Status of Clinical Operations, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-10-06; MS269.000194; School of Dental Medicine; 1 Web sites
  - Faculty Academic Continuity Responsibilities Relating to COVID-19, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-03-31; MS269.000195; Office of the President; 1 Web sites
  - Frequently Asked Questions on COVID-19 for New Students, Scholars, and Employees, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-10-06; MS269.000196; International Center; 1 Web sites
  - Hardship Fund for Medical, PH, and PD Students, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-09-15; MS269.000197; Tufts Crowdfunding; 1 Web sites
  - Important COVID-19 Guidance from Tufts Veterinary Field Service, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-04-10; MS269.000198; Cummings Veterinary Medical Center; 1 Web sites
  - Important Information on the COVID-19 Outbreak from GSBS, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-03-31; MS269.000199; Graduate School of Biomedical Sciences; 1 Web sites
  - Live updates: Tufts community responds to coronavirus, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-10-06; MS269.000200; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Mutual Aid Facebook, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-10-06; MS269.000201; Tufts Mutual Aid; 1 Web sites
  - Unexpected Hardship Fund for GSBS Students, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-09-15; MS269.000202; Tufts Crowdfunding; 1 Web sites
  - Unexpected Hardship Fund for Student Needs, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-09-15; MS269.000203; Tufts Crowdfunding; 1 Web sites
  - Update to Commencement 2020, 2020-03-18 -- 2020-10-06; MS269.000204; Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - Events & Exhibitions: Tufts University Art Galleries, 2020-03-21 -- 2020-09-03; MS269.000205; School of the Museum of Fine Arts; 1 Web sites
  - BREAKING: Tufts student tests positive for COVID-19, 2020-03-23 -- 2020-03-31; MS269.000206; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - If Coronavirus Patients Overwhelm Hospitals, These Colleges Are Offering Their Dorms, 2020-03-23 -- 2020-03-31; MS269.000207; The Chronicle of Higher Education; 1 Web sites
  - School of Medicine, Tufts Medical Center swing into action in response to COVID-19, 2020-03-23 -- 2020-03-31; MS269.000208; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Spirit of the Creative: Last-minute show before campus closure, 2020-03-23 -- 2020-03-31; MS269.000209; Spirit of the Creative; 1 Web sites
  - Spring sports canceled, winter NCAA competitions to continue, 2020-03-23 -- 2020-03-31; MS269.000210; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Students asked to move out of residence halls by Monday, extensions possible, 2020-03-23 -- 2020-03-31; MS269.000211; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Community Rallies to Support Students in Need, 2020-03-23 -- 2020-03-31; MS269.000212; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts is prepared to house patients during the coronavirus outbreak, other colleges and universities should too, 2020-03-23 -- 2020-03-31; MS269.000213; The Boston Globe; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Mutual Aid steps up to assist students amid move out orders, 2020-03-23 -- 2020-03-31; MS269.000214; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts student being tested for COVID-19, 3 positives in Somerville, Medford - The Tufts Daily, 2020-03-23 -- 2020-03-31; MS269.000215; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts students abroad struggle to get home as world's borders close, 2020-03-23 -- 2020-03-31; MS269.000216; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts suspends Global Education program, exchange students to return home, 2020-03-23 -- 2020-03-31; MS269.000217; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts suspends in-person classes, asks students not to return after spring break, 2020-03-23 -- 2020-03-31; MS269.000218; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts, union in talks over dining workers' status during closure, 2020-03-23 -- 2020-03-31; MS269.000219; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - We're Self-Centered: Coronavirus and Conceiving Asian America, 2020-03-23 -- 2020-03-31; MS269.000220; Tufts Observer; 1 Web sites
  - Confusion, anger rife as low-income international students among those forced off campus, 2020-03-31 -- 2020-04-06; MS269.000221; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 Information for the A&S Community, 2020-03-31 -- 2020-04-06; MS269.000222; School of Arts and Sciences; 1 Web sites
  - Editorial: Tufts community supports students in need, filling void left by Tufts administration, 2020-03-31 -- 2020-04-06; MS269.000223; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Faculty choose optional pass/fail over mandatory, 2020-03-31 -- 2020-04-06; MS269.000224; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Form to Submit Ideas for Virtual Commencement, 2020-03-31 -- 2020-04-06; MS269.000225; Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - Monaco vows to house patients, respond to local needs as coronavirus outbreak worsens, 2020-03-31 -- 2020-04-06; MS269.000226; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Netflix and cold pizza: Tufts quarantines dozens of students, 2020-03-31 -- 2020-04-06; MS269.000227; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Op-ed: Course guidelines proposal for the spring 2020 semester, 2020-03-31 -- 2020-04-06; MS269.000228; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Op-ed: The need for equitable grading policies in the face of COVID-19, 2020-03-31 -- 2020-04-06; MS269.000229; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Op-ed: The need for equitable grading policies in the face of COVID-19, 2020-03-31 -- 2020-04-06; MS269.000230; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Petition for Pass/Fail Semester, 2020-03-31; MS269.000231; 1 Web sites
  - Petition for Tufts to Reschedule Graduation, 2020-03-31; MS269.000232; 1 Web sites
  - Team Comes Together to Repair Thousands of N-95 Masks, 2020-03-31 -- 2020-04-06; MS269.000233; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Transcript: Tufts administrators discuss university response to coronavirus pandemic, 2020-03-31 -- 2020-04-06; MS269.000234; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - TTS Guide to Learning Remotely During Online Classes, 2020-03-31 -- 2020-04-06; MS269.000235; Tufts Technology Services; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts administrators discuss university response to coronavirus pandemic, 2020-03-31 -- 2020-04-06; MS269.000236; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Mutual Aid for Students Affected by COVID-19, 2020-03-31; MS269.000237; Tufts Mutual Aid; 1 Web sites
  - TUSC Coronavirus Updates, 2020-03-31 -- 2020-04-06; MS269.000238; Tufts University Social Collective; 1 Web sites
  - TUSC Virtual Events Listing, 2020-03-31 -- 2020-04-06; MS269.000239; Tufts University Social Collective; 1 Web sites
  - We're trying to catch up: Governments enforce strict regulations on communities as COVID-19 worsens, 2020-03-31 -- 2020-04-06; MS269.000240; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 Announcement: International Center Temporarily Transitioning to Virtual Operations, 2020-04-01; MS269.000241; International Center; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19: Guide to Virtual Operations, 2020-04-01; MS269.000242; International Center; 1 Web sites
  - FAQs for International Students Following the March 10 Announcement, 2020-04-01; MS269.000243; International Center; 1 Web sites
  - Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs) about COVID-19 and OPT, 2020-04-01; MS269.000244; International Center; 1 Web sites
  - International Center COVID-19 Information Page and Travel FAQs, 2020-04-01; MS269.000245; International Center; 1 Web sites
  - International Center Resource Page on Coronavirus, 2020-04-01; MS269.000246; International Center; 1 Web sites
  - Message to International Students and Scholars from Iran Regarding COVID-19 (March 2, 2020), 2020-04-01; MS269.000247; International Center; 1 Web sites
  - Message to Students from China (Feb 27, 2020), 2020-04-01; MS269.000248; International Center; 1 Web sites
  - NCAA Cancels All Winter and Spring Championships, 2020-04-01; MS269.000249; Department of Athletics; 1 Web sites
  - Thank You, 2020-04-01; MS269.000250; Office of the President; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University Commencement 2020, 2020-04-01; MS269.000251; Office of the President; 1 Web sites
  - Update for F-1 International Students from the International Center, 2020-04-01; MS269.000252; International Center; 1 Web sites
  - US-Canada-Mexico Border Travel Restrictions, 2020-04-01; MS269.000253; International Center; 1 Web sites
  - Arts faculty innovate in wake of transition to remote learning, miss community of in-person classes, 2020-04-06; MS269.000254; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Boston Students Help Repair Medical Masks After Tufts Receives Damaged Donation, 2020-04-06; MS269.000255; WBUR; 1 Web sites
  - COVID-19 Update · Inside Admissions, 2020-04-06; MS269.000256; Undergraduate Admissions; 1 Web sites
  - Following opposition to virtual ceremony, Tufts to reschedule Commencement, 2020-04-06; MS269.000257; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Helping local hospitals and communities respond to the COVID-19 surge, 2020-04-06; MS269.000258; Office of the President; 1 Web sites
  - Important Announcement about Commencement for 2020 Graduates, 2020-04-06; MS269.000259; Office of the President; 1 Web sites
  - In Defense of Online Defenses, 2020-04-06; MS269.000260; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Jumbo Month Offerings (online alternative to Jumbo Days), 2020-04-06 -- 2020-08-31; MS269.000261; Undergraduate Admissions; 1 Web sites
  - Language departments, faculty adapt to online learning, 2020-04-06; MS269.000262; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - New Students and Scholars: COVID-19 and Your I-20 or DS-2019, 2020-04-06; MS269.000263; International Center; 1 Web sites
  - Op-ed: Tufts can do better than virtual commencement, 2020-04-06; MS269.000264; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Research, teaching assistants continue work as university suspends on-campus research, 2020-04-06; MS269.000265; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - TCU Senate budgeting, elections to continue, 2020-04-06; MS269.000266; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Parents in China Donate 31,000 N95 Masks, 2020-04-06; MS269.000267; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Administrators, student organizers partner to aid disadvantaged students, 2020-04-13; MS269.000268; Tufts Daily; 1 Web sites
  - Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine at Tufts University sends personal protective equipment, ventilators and other medical supplies to area healthcare facilities to aid with COVID-19 efforts, 2020-04-13; MS269.000269; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites
  - Embassy Contact Information for J-1 Exchange Visitors, 2020-04-13; MS269.000270; International Center; 1 Web sites
  - Higher Education's Role in Fighting the Coronavirus, 2020-04-13; MS269.000271; Tufts Now; 1 Web sites